CJ ENM presents
in association with UNION INVESTMENT
PARTNERS, KC VENTURES Co., Ltd.,
MICHIGAN VENTURE CAPITAL Co., Ltd.,
ISU VENTURE CAPITAL, CJ CGV,
GAIA VENTURE PARTNERS LLC,
TIMEWISE INVESTMENT
an iFilm Co., Ltd. and
TORY PICTURES production
Executive Producer
TEDDY JUNG, JUNG HYUN
JANG SEOK-BIN, LEE SUK-JOON
SEO YEA-JI
KIM KANG-WOO
Provided by Synchronized
RECALLED
Pulse is normal.
Pupils look normal.
Ms. Kim?
If you can hear me, please blink.
Do you recognize your husband?
Soo Jin...
You'll get better soon.
DAD PASSED AWAY: 2001.12.06
MOM PASSED AWAY: 1993.03.08
What?
So I'm not the only child
of a mogul.
But an orphan?
That's sad.
(NO SIBLINGS)
But I was always by your side.
When did you first tell me
you love me?
I couldn't.
Not at the wedding
or even before.
Why not?
You'll see...
I'm scared.
What if I meet someone
who knows me?
We practiced many times.
Let's try it again.
If it's a woman...
'Oh, my! Long time no see!'
'You got prettier!
I didn't recognize you!'
If it's a man?
'Who are you?'
BIG SALE ON UNSOLD UNITS!
We're here.
We have a big load.
I'll take some up first.
Stay here.
I'll be right back.
Ground floor.
Tenth floor.
Going up.
Help!
Help...
Is anyone there?
What the?
Help me...
Soo Jin!
Wake up!
What's wrong?
Soo Jin!
Are you okay?
- What happened?
- The power went out.
You hate being in the dark.
Let's go back to
the hospital tomorrow.
What's that?
Today's May 10th.
The day you came home.
It's all melted.
Remember?
From what you told me,
is that Canada?
Yup.
Who suggested emigrating
to Canada first?
Well, let's see.
You suggested going first.
So I made preparations.
I want to hear more.
Well,
Vermillion Lake is reddish orange.
When the sunset
reflects off the lake,
everything is stained red.
When winds blow down
the mountains to the lake,
they say it sounds like
someone's singing.
Next, please.
Coming.
Even if you can immigrate,
your work experience won't count.
Are you willing
to start from the bottom?
Yes, sir. I'll do anything.
You bought a house
even before the screening.
Is there a reason
you're rushing to immigrate?
The reason?
I'm bored.
I thought I'd take a walk.
What if you get lost alone?
See you later.
Going down.
Soo Jin!
Third floor.
Going down.
Hi.
No!
What did the doctor say?
To stay in the hospital, right?
But you insisted on
being discharged.
You're not well!
You have to be careful.
If you don't listen,
I'll make you stay in the hospital
until we move to Canada.
You're hurt worse than me.
- Sit here.
- What?
Sit down.
- I'm fine.
- Come on!
It's okay.
Why'd you do that back then?
I...
Wait.
You didn't take your pills.
They've prescribed
what's good for you.
Take them.
(DREAM TOWN PROJECT - CANCELLED)
See over there?
They cut the CCTV
and took the copper pipes.
They stole this and this too.
I was at a nearby pub
and came back to check.
The materials were gone by then.
You said this place
will be demolished soon?
Yes.
- That's why I came to...
- At night?
You work really hard.
What?
You came back at 1AM to check?
Did you hide gold here
or something?
I already told you, detective.
The owner was coming
to inspect.
What are you implying?
Please, sir.
I apologize.
Please send us the list of
missing materials.
Names of all workers.
The workers' list too.
Subcontractors too.
Subcontractors too, please.
Kim Soo Jin.
Housewife.
Kid!
Going up.
It's you!
At the crosswalk yesterday...
Were you hurt?
Did you go and see a doctor?
- Third floor.
- Wait...
My princess is back.
Mommy! I'm hungry!
- Had fun at school?
- Yes!
SAMJEONG ARCHITECTS
- Hello?
- Can you come now?
I know this sounds crazy.
But just in case...
I have to do something.
No!
I saw it happen.
I know it sounds weird.
It's crazy.
Though it's very rare,
there are cases of hallucinations
due to cerebral cortex damage.
Due to your brain injury,
you may think you saw the future.
But I did...
Soo Jin.
Stop it, please?
She could misconceive things.
Like you've seen
or heard them before.
They call it déjà vu.
It's like a delusion.
No matter what I say,
you think I'm crazy.
Soo Jin! Wait!
I'm sorry.
Soo Jin!
Don't go like that.
The third-floor kid.
What?
The third-floor girl is alive!
Even if what you say is true,
it doesn't concern you.
But the girl almost died.
What if I could stop it?
You said she's fine.
Where is she?
They're gone!
I just saw them...
That's enough!
You're not okay!
Right.
I'm not okay.
Soo Jin.
- Wait.
- Let's go.
I need some air.
I overreacted earlier.
I'm sorry.
I should only say good things...
Do I know how to swim?
- Swim?
- Yes.
Well...
- Let's try and see.
- Now?
Here?
Wait! It's cold.
The water is still too cold!
I think it'll be warm.
Soo Jin.
It's cold. Stop going in!
Let's go back!
It's dangerous.
Come on. Let's go back.
I like it.
Are you okay?
Guess I couldn't swim.
I'm scared.
No, you loved the water.
You liked going to the beach
every summer.
You love lakes too.
Now. Relax.
I'll hold you.
Don't let me go.
That's it.
- Are you still there?
- Yup.
I'll always be by your side.
Even if you can't see me.
HEAT IT UP BEFORE YOU EAT
DON'T FORGET YOUR PILLS
It's the police.
We've received a report
from your hospital.
OPEN DOOR
It looks like a model home.
Pardon?
Ms. Kim.
The report said you had bruises.
Here.
It could be from the accident.
But some could be from
before you fell.
We're asking about your husband.
Like, if he's abusive or violent...
I'll report him.
Pardon?
If he is, I'll report him.
You had me.
I'm sorry.
You went hiking together?
Yes.
But I heard you lost your memory.
Sir.
I'm sorry.
Everything is fine, right?
Yes.
Please sign here.
Don't worry.
It's just a formality
for us to check on reports.
I see.
LEE JI-HOON, BORN 1982.05.21
MAY 20TH
KIM SOO JIN
Call us if you need anything.
I will.
We'll be going.
Isn't it the other way?
Sorry?
Let's go.
- We'll be in touch.
- Bye.
Hello?
Ji-hoon, what do you like?
Why all of a sudden?
Well, you know a lot about me,
but I don't know
anything about you.
Don't worry.
You'll remember everything soon.
PRESENT YOURSELF
WITH A TRIP TO CANADA
Ground floor.
Going up.
Here.
MILITARY MAIL
Help me! Let go!
Seventh floor.
No! Wait!
Something terrible
could happen to you.
Left neck...
No, he has a scar on his chin.
In his 40s, no 50s.
The man will...
Who's there?
That man will...
It's me, Dad.
Wait...
Soo Jin!
It's been a while.
How've you been?
You got prettier,
I didn't recognize you, ma'am.
Why are you calling me ma'am?
Know how much I
worried about you?
I had no way to reach you.
Did I lose some weight?
Really?
You don't remember anything?
I can't believe it.
Hello, Ms. Kim!
It's Chae-min.
You don't remember?
You worked here for years!
I worked here, ma'am?
Stop calling me that!
Then saying I got prettier
was a lie?
You can't remember your desk?
It's here.
See? Who's this?
Tell me again.
You went climbing
with your husband?
His love for you is quite unique.
Did he get suspicious of you again?
What do you mean?
Some people lie about going
mountain climbing,
and end up climbing
something else at motels.
Since you go hiking often,
he could get jealous or suspicious.
Because he's a doting husband.
A jealous but doting husband.
KIM SOO JIN, INSTRUCTOR
LEE JI-HOON, CEO OF SAMJEONG
I'll send your stuff by post.
Are you sure you're okay?
SAMJEONG ARCHITECTS
Oh, no.
Did you lose money too?
You should've come sooner.
It went bankrupt and closed
over 6 months ago.
A man comes once in a while
to pick stuff up.
DREAM TOWN FOR SALE
You're too late.
JI-HOON
CHO KI-SANG, NAMYANGJU POLICE
Hi.
Where'd you go?
Why didn't you take my calls?
Where were you today?
Did you go to my office?
Emigrating to Canada...
Is it because you went bankrupt?
It's not like that.
I didn't want to worry you.
Things are wrapping up.
I'll take care of everything
before leaving for Canada.
By the way,
how'd you find your way
to my office?
I went to my art school.
Your memory...
...is back?
Is that a problem?
What do you mean?
Know what I thought about all day?
You even told me
about my sleeping habits.
But you didn't tell me
where I worked?
You know I can't remember.
Am I really who you say I am?
I couldn't tell you.
Truth is...
You're the one
who painted that.
I didn't lie on purpose.
Due to the accident,
you injured your finger.
They said you may never
be able to paint again.
I knew you'd be devastated.
That's why I couldn't tell you.
I was going to tell you
when you got better.
Thanks to you,
I don't remember anything.
It's all mixed up in my head.
I keep seeing things.
I can't tell if they're delusions
or reality now.
Watch, sir.
This is the only way
to the site on the 13th.
Jeez.
Are you looking for
a serial killer or what?
See that?
It's the chief's truck.
Here! It's the only car
that came out of the site.
Did you check the list
of stolen goods?
I can't go through all of it
by myself.
Then how can they be
all on that car?
Eat it.
The stolen goods must've been sold.
Look into buyers of the goods.
Even if sold separately,
it's enough to catch eyes.
- Wait!
- Why?
What is it?
It's him.
Someone you know?
Can't remember?
The wedding picture!
PASSPORT
Here you are.
ME / SOO JIN
I'm sorry.
Not getting on?
I'm almost home.
I raised her long enough
for her dead mom.
I'll send her to a bar or something.
She's pretty.
Takes after her mom.
I'll call you back.
Shit.
Just my damn luck!
Let go!
Don't touch the girl!
What?
If anything happens to her,
I'll report you.
Who are you?
Who the hell are you!
Soo Jin!
Are you okay?
Unit 706.
Unit 706...
Preconstruction here sold
like hot cakes.
Who knew it'd be demolished?
Up this way, please.
Are you talking about Lee Ji-hoon?
Yes, that's him.
The CEO of Samjeong,
the architect in charge.
When this went bankrupt,
he went into hiding
from loan sharks.
No one knows where he is.
Jeez.
- Get back!
- Jeez!
No safety fences? Crazy!
- Detective Bae.
- Yes?
Didn't that woman say
she fell while hiking?
- Who?
- You know.
Right. Lee Ji-hoon's wife.
So...
Is Mr. Lee the suspect?
Everyone in this project
is a suspect.
Especially you, chief.
The man from unit 706...
He'll die.
He tried to kill the girl
and me.
The man on the seventh floor...
Soo Jin!
Who are you calling?
Calm down. Please?
Nothing happened.
If anything happens,
I'll take care of it.
Ji-hoon?
Help!
You live in unit 1005, right?
Yes.
Someone found this
in the elevator.
Hey.
Good! You're up.
Let's have breakfast.
Last night...
Where did you go?
Where would I go?
I slept beside you.
Are you okay?
Sit down.
Let's eat quickly.
I have a busy day ahead.
What was Ji-hoon like?
Did something happen?
Did he hit you again?
You really don't remember, do you?
When you said you'd quit
for about a month,
you told me you'll get divorced.
Saying your husband
has changed.
You were taking pills
for depression
because of it.
By chance,
was I seeing another man?
That I don't know.
But your husband thought so.
Are you okay?
Did you get the box?
The parcel?
Someone found it in the elevator.
I gave it to your husband.
When?
Last night.
It was past 2AM.
Was he going on a trip?
He left with a big suitcase.
Yes.
You want to change your flight?
I don't mind transferring.
I'll even pay for new tickets.
Book us the earliest flight, please.
Let me check.
KIM SOO JIN
POLICE STATION
What do you mean?
He snuck out a big suitcase
from unit 706.
He took it down the stairs.
It looked heavy.
But inside...
The man from unit 706...
His body must've been there.
Why do you think
his body was in the bag?
I heard screams.
I heard them fight.
I know I sound crazy.
But I saw the man dying.
No.
I saw that he would die.
Let me get this straight.
So the man who lives in unit 706
was murdered.
- Right?
- Yes.
And you saw the killer, right?
Yes.
Did you see the killer's face?
Soo Jin!
- Wait, sir!
- It's him!
He killed the man from unit 706.
What are you talking about?
I saw it.
I saw you coming out of
that man's apartment!
You're seeing things.
Remember what the doctor said?
You're making stuff up
like it really happened.
- Let's go.
- Hang on a second!
How did you know
she was here?
That's odd.
After her accident,
I got worried.
So, I set up a tracking app.
Can I take her now?
Wait.
We're not sure what's going on.
But she says she saw a corpse.
It's our job to check on it.
Fine.
Then let's all go and check.
That'll solve everything.
It can't be.
I swear I saw him!
Ms. Kim?
Unit 706 was never sold.
It's been empty.
There are a lot of unsold units
in this building.
Can we go now?
Soo Jin.
- Ms. Kim.
- Soo Jin.
Just one question.
Why'd you go to the construction site
on the 13th?
Do I have to answer that?
Soo Jin!
We're leaving for Canada
in two days.
I booked an earlier flight.
Everything will get better there.
Get some rest.
I have things to wrap up.
When I come back,
let's forget everything and leave.
Tenth floor.
Ground floor.
Going down.
Ninth floor.
Yes. I'm on my way down.
Please stop coming to my house.
You gave me no choice.
- I'm sorry.
- Look!
Stamp it now!
Do what I say to pay me back.
Right?
I'll pay you back soon.
I'm sorry it's late.
Do it tonight.
Soo Jin.
I was so worried about you.
Where were you?
Let's go in.
Did you see our ID stamps?
Our stamps?
You have an awesome memory.
While you were gone,
I thought about what you said.
I'll answer you later.
Let's meet at the site at 8PM.
Don't go there.
What?
You could get killed.
What do you mean?
Are you trying to scare me?
See you later.
UNIT 903 TO. LEE JI-HOON
Lee Ji-hoon...
TO. KIM SOO JIN
Kim Soo Jin...
There are over 100 workers.
Why pick on me?
You stole the goods bit by bit
and pretended you didn't know.
I saw the CCTV footages.
You did it many times, chief.
Thanks to you,
we checked out all
the material dealer shops.
Selling off that much stuff
would've raised red flags.
But we found nothing.
You didn't sell them.
You put them in storage
to sneak them out slowly,
didn't you!
You erased the CCTV every time.
But...
why'd you break
the CCTV that night?
The CCTV wasn't me!
Okay!
You admit to the rest, right?
Order some food for him too.
He just confessed.
It can't be over $5.
That's not it!
That night,
I saw someone.
SAMJEONG ARCHITECTS
DREAM TOWN
NAMYANGJOO ROAD 861
KIM SOO JIN
Yes?
Detective.
Someone is about to be killed.
I know it's hard to believe.
About to be killed?
Didn't happen yet?
- Yes.
- Where are you?
Dream Town construction site.
I'll call you back.
What did you just say?
Right.
I know whose car it was.
- Lee Ji-hoon?
- Yes.
It was definitely his car.
I'm not certain because of the hat,
but the driver seemed to be...
Excuse me!
Mr. Kim Sun-woo?
Kim Sun-woo?
Yes, that's him.
Jackass.
Why are you here?
Soo Jin!
Stop! Soo Jin!
Where are you?
Come out!
Why are you here?
It's dangerous! Let's go!
Soo Jin?
Soo Jin...
Stay back!
Why'd you kill him?
Why!
Who are you?
The man you killed...
Is it Ji-hoon?
Let's go down.
I'll explain everything.
Who the hell are you!
You have to believe me, please.
No.
I don't trust you.
You're just a murderer.
Stay back!
Stop!
Soo Jin...
Soo Jin, no!
We'll be in Canada in two days.
It'll be all over then.
I did all this for you.
Stay back!
Soo Jin, no!
No!
- Stop!
- Ms. Kim!
- Get down!
- Are you okay?
He killed a man.
The body is here.
No...
It can't be.
I swear I saw everything!
I know what I saw!
Stop it!
There's no dead body!
Looks like she's got it wrong again.
He's lying!
No!
I saw everything.
See!
I saw it.
I swear I saw it!
I know what I saw...
You're hallucinating.
Now, stop it.
No...
I swear I saw it.
I know what I saw!
I saw everything!
- Stop!
- Let go!
Let me go!
- Calm down!
- Stop!
Stop it!
Get up. Let's go.
Are you happy now?
I'm taking my wife home.
Stop.
What wife, you bastard!
You broke the CCTV
on the 13th, didn't you?
- Hold him.
- What?
- Get him!
- Yes, sir.
Why rack your brain?
Just dig till you find the answer.
But, sir... Wait!
Kim Sun-woo!
What did you do!
Let me meet him, please?
Of course. Let's go.
Ms. Kim?
Are you okay?
The company went bankrupt
due to Lee Ji-hoon's gambling debt.
We fought about that at the site.
And I killed him by accident.
Why'd you go back to the site?
Once demolition starts,
I worried the body would be found,
so I went back.
I planned to kill Soo Jin
for her insurance money.
So I acted like I was Lee Ji-hoon.
Here.
He bought his current place
4 months ago.
Your real house is in Seoul.
If you go there, maybe
you'll remember something.
Kim Sun-woo.
Who is he?
He's your adoptive older brother.
I don't think
all your stories were lies.
What does that matter now?
Think whatever you want.
Though I was adopted,
you're the only family I have.
Tell me.
What in the world happened?
I don't know what you mean.
I killed your husband.
I planned to kill you
for your insurance payout.
If you died on the mountain,
I would've walked free.
It's too bad.
If what I saw at the site
is a memory of actual events,
it means I was there that night.
Memory?
Can you tell
what's real from what's made up?
Do you think you're sane?
I have nothing more to say.
Let's end it.
Escort her out.
Cut the nonsense and just leave.
Let's go.
Unit 706.
What about what I saw there?
Kid!
Wait.
Are you okay?
Soo Jin!
Is your name Soo Jin too?
Yes, I'm Choi Soo Jin.
It's Kim Soo Jin now.
Kim Sun-woo's little sister.
Kim Soo Jin.
That should do for
Lee Ji-hoon's case.
Unit 706...
This is her adoption record.
Let's see.
Kim Tae-jun lived in unit 706.
Son, Kim Sun-woo.
Then it says Kim Tae-jun
went missing.
CERTIFICATE OF ADOPTION
Where is Kim Tae-jun?
KIM SOO JIN
Bitch!
Sun-woo...
Soo Jin.
Go to Ji-hoon's dorm now.
If he asks, tell him I sent you.
Just say you came right
after school.
How can I?
It's because of me!
This happened because of me!
It's not your fault.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Just stay focused.
Listen to me.
You never came home today.
If the cops ask,
say you don't know.
Got it?
Sun-woo...
Yeah?
I'm at the location you told me.
We found Kim Tae-jun.
SEOUL SEOCHO-GU
WEVE CONDO #903
Soo Jin! Where are you?
Your husband came and
wreaked havoc looking for you!
He was screaming
like a madman!
Soo Jin!
You're alive?
Did you think I'd die
without you two?
Soo Jin! Stop!
You put your father in a suitcase...
KIM SOO JIN
Yes?
Lee Ji-hoon is alive!
What? Lee Ji-hoon is dead.
Ms. Kim?
I don't know what you saw,
but calm down.
Lee Ji-hoon is alive!
Hello?
Ms. Kim?
Stay back.
Stay back!
Sir!
- It's not Lee Ji-hoon.
- What?
Forensics called.
The body is not Lee Ji-hoon's.
- Take the call, sir.
- Shit!
Then where the hell is he?
We were happy once.
Right.
The art director said
you don't remember anything.
You always looked at me like that.
Know how much it hurt me?
What are you saying?
Soo Jin...
How could you be so selfish?
Don't you remember?
Mr. Lee.
If you stamped this for me earlier,
I didn't have to give you
the special treatment.
INSURED PERSON: KIM SOO JIN
BENEFICIARY: LEE JI-HOON
I'm sorry.
So?
How will you kill her?
I'm sorry. I can...
The interest goes up by the day.
Today's our anniversary.
I will tell my wife
how much I love her.
When she learns the truth,
my wife, who's been deceiving me,
will jump down.
Or she'll beg forgiveness
and come back to me.
What the fuck are you saying?
Jackass!
I told you to wait!
I warned you!
I said wait, son of a bitch!
Soo Jin.
Soo Jin!
Stay back.
- I can explain!
- Stop!
I can explain everything!
CANADA IMMIGRATION GUIDE
You're leaving with Sun-woo?
That's why you wanted a divorce?
Soo Jin, no!
This is crazy!
Stop it.
You're crazy!
Crazy?
How can I not go crazy
stuck between you two?
You think I'm crazy?
I'm crazy because of you two!
You and Sun-woo!
What the hell!
- Give me your car!
- Where are you going?
- Put an APB on a car.
- What car?
Mine! Hurry!
Are you okay?
It's all right.
It's okay.
What now?
Back then and now...
you haven't changed.
You decide and take
responsibility all by yourself.
Soo Jin.
I'm sorry, Sun-woo.
It's because of me...
No!
No...
Forgive me.
No!
Soo Jin!
What are you doing?
I've always been curious.
Sun-woo and me...
I wonder who loves you more.
How Sun-woo wants to save you.
And how I want to kill you.
They're all for love, aren't they?
Too bad Sun-woo
didn't see this.
No!
No...
Where is she!
Where's Soo Jin, you bastard?
You should ask me nicely
at a time like this.
You asshole!
You're too late.
Go wait in hell!
Over there!
Soo Jin...
Damn it!
Stop! Come here!
Stay still!
Soo Jin!
Where are you?
Are you okay?
Wake up!
Soo Jin...
Where's the fire coming from?
Unit 903 is on fire.
Soo Jin.
Soo Jin?
- Sun-woo...
- Yes, it's me.
You came?
It's okay.
Oh, no!
I'm fine.
I remember everything now.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
It's not your fault.
Don't look back.
Soo Jin...
Go to Canada.
Sun-woo...
Where's my brother?
Mr. Kim Sun-woo
was found dead.
He covered you from the flames.
To save you.
MAY HE REST IN PEACE
There's a flash drive inside.
We received it from
the Canadian embassy.
Take a look when you get well.
Is there a reason
you're rushing to immigrate?
The reason?
I made a promise when I was young.
I forgot about it,
but she remembered.
Remember?
SOO JIN, LET'S LIVE HERE LATER
(SOO JIN, LET'S LIVE HERE LATER)
You gave it to me.
What?
You still have this?
It's Vermilion Lake.
It's in Canada.
When I was young,
I had a recurring dream.
Playing in a pretty house
by that lake
with you.
That dream
became my memory
that got me through rough times.
Soo Jin...
Listen.
I'm leaving for Canada.
I want to start over there.
I want to move there...
and give her a chance
to start over.
Even if I can't,
she has to go.
Please. She has to go.
SOO JIN, LET'S LIVE HERE LATER
There...
our memories await us.
Great. Now for the bride's family.
Is there no other family?
It's just us.
I'm her brother.
Okay, then.
Your eyes are red.
Don't want to send her off?
Ah... No...
Really? Did you cry?
No way.
Look up.
Mister?
The groom stands to her right.
Could you stand to her left?
Ah, there? Sure.
Don't want to send me off?
Then why are you?
Should I not?
Look over here, please.
One, two, three!
Directed by SEO YOU-MIN
Provided by Synchronized
RECALLED